{
    "id": "cf15b7d47fb7439dbeeca85167c6f6df",
    "title": "Infinitives with and without to",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c5849d3c1d8b4a40823080e2917681b1",
            "title": "Infinitives With And Without To",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I would rather ………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wait",
                        "to wait",
                        "waiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ought …………………. your ways.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "mend",
                        "to mend"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She didn’t ………………. anything.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "say",
                        "to say"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was told ………………. the room.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "leave",
                        "to leave"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better ………………….. what she wants.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "to see"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t let my children ………………….. up late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stay",
                        "to stay"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I didn’t see him ...................... in.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "come",
                        "to come"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We both heard her ……………….. that she was leaving.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "say",
                        "to say"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Did you feel the earth ………………….?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "move",
                        "to move"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you help me ………………… the car?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "load",
                        "to load",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}